(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
名前のない怪物
Monster With No Name
作詞・作曲：ryo(supercell)
Lyrics & Composition: ryo(supercell)
震えてるわ 指先
Your fingertips are trembling...
死んだみたい
...as if they were dead.
煉獄の淵で
At the edge of purgatory...
うまく歌えなくて
...unable to sing well.
霧に煙る夜
On a night hazy with mist...
浮かび上がった月
...the moon emerged.
鏡を見て 私を
Look in the mirror... at me.
目を逸らさないで
Don't look away.
黒い鉄格子の中から
From within the black iron bars...
私は生まれてきたんだ
...I was born.
悪意の代償を願いの望むがままにお前に
To you, the price of malice, as your wishes desire.
さあ 讃えよ 正義を壊して
Now, praise it—destroy justice.
壊される前に
Before it's destroyed...
因果の代償を払って
...pay the price of karma...
共に行こう 名前のない怪物
...and let's go together, monster with no name.
耳鳴りがしてる
My ears are ringing.
鉄条網うるさくて
The barbed wire is noisy.
思い出せないの
I can't remember...
あの日の戦慄
...the shiver of that day.
雨はまだ止まない
The rain still hasn't stopped.
何も見えないの
I can't see anything.
鏡見て こんなに
Look in the mirror... I've grown...
大きくなったの
...this much.
黒い雨 降らしこの空
This sky raining black rain...
私は望まれないもの
...I am something unwanted.
ひび割れた音色 罪 愛しどうぞ 傍観者たちに
The cracked melody, loving the sin, please, to the bystanders...
さあ いま 震え正義を消せない
Now, tremble—justice cannot be erased.
傷を抱きしめて この身体を受け入れて
Embrace the wounds and accept this body.
共に行こう 名前のない怪物
Let's go together, monster with no name.
名前のない怪物
The Nameless Monster
神は
The god
告げる
proclaims
真我
The true self
世界を！
The world!
睦言の中で私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born amidst sweet whispers
紅色の代償願い望むがままに
The price is crimson, just as I wished and desired
お前に
To you
さあ絶えよう 正義を壊して壊される前に
Come, let's fade away; destroy justice before being destroyed
因果の代償払い報いを守る名もなき怪物
Paying the price of karma, a nameless monster guarding the retribution
曇り雨降らせこの空
Let cloudy rain fall from this sky
私は望まれないもの
I am an unwanted thing
ひび割れた音じゃ愛せない僕の足跡
I can't love my footprints with this cracked sound
この身体を受け入れ共にゆこう 名前のない怪物
Accept this body and let's go together, nameless monster
はい！ということで皆さん、こんやっぴー！
Yes! So everyone, Konyappi!
こんやっぴー！
Konyappi!
ホロライブ4期生の、常闇トワ様でーす！
It's Hololive 4th Gen's Tokoyami Towa-sama!
ちょっと待って、水飲もうかな。水飲もう。
Wait a sec, I'll drink some water. Let's drink water.
バーチャル、バーチャルウォーター。w
Virtual, virtual water. lol
ということで、今日はトワ様の誕生日でーす！
So, today is Towa-sama's birthday!
イェーイ！皆見てるー？
Yay! Is everyone watching?
ていうか待機所でさ、TMT打ちすぎだから。
I mean, you guys were typing TMT too much in the waiting room.
やめてちょっと！
Stop it, seriously!
もう、今年はほら、TMTを脱出したいっていう話をしてたから、
I mean, I said I wanted to escape being called TMT this year,
皆がそれをやめないと終わらないわけですよ。
so if you all don't stop, it won't ever end.
やめてくださいよ本当に。最低ですよ！ドン！
Please stop, seriously. You're the worst! Bam!
っていうのを一人でやるのもすごいとても寂しいんですけど。w
Doing this routine alone is actually pretty lonely. lol
はい、あの最初に歌った曲はね、『名前のない怪物』を歌わせていただきました。
Right, for the first song, I sang 'The Nameless Monster'.
今日はね、トワはこの後もう一曲ソロで歌って、その後にゲストパートに行くんですけど、
Today, I'll sing one more solo song, and then move on to the guest part.
今日はね、かっこいい曲から可愛い曲まで準備してるので、
I've prepared everything from cool songs to cute songs today,
ぜひぜひ最後まで聴いていってもらえると嬉しいでーす！
so I'd be happy if you'd listen until the very end!
あとこれ！#常闇トワ生誕祭2021 これいっぱい呟いてね！
Also this! Please tweet with #常闇トワ生誕祭2021 a lot!
ということでね、ちょっと落ち着いてから次の曲に行きたいなと思います。
So, I'll take a moment to settle down before moving to the next song.
次の曲はね、かっこいい曲ですから。
The next one is a cool song.
めちゃめちゃ難しいから、うまく歌えるか心配なんですけど、頑張ります。
It's super difficult, so I'm worried if I can sing it well, but I'll do my best.
それでは聴いてください、unravel。
Now please listen to, unravel.
教えてよ 教えてよ その仕組みを
Tell me, tell me, how it works
僕の中に誰がいるの？
Who is inside of me?
壊れた 壊れたよ この世界で
Broken, I'm broken, in this world
君が笑う 何も見えずに
You're laughing, seeing nothing
壊れた僕なんてさ
A broken me...
息を止めて
Stop breathing
ほどけない もうほどけないよ
Can't unravel, can't unravel anymore
真実さえ
Even the truth
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない あなたを見つけて
Can break, can't break, can go mad, can't go mad, I found you
揺れた歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は
In a shaking, distorted world, I'm gradually...
透き通って見えなくなって
Becoming transparent and invisible
見つけないで 僕のことを
Don't find me
見つめないで
Don't stare at me
誰かが描いた世界の中で
In a world someone else drew
あなたを傷つけたくはないよ
I don't want to hurt you
覚えていて 僕のことを
Remember me
無限に広がる孤独が絡まる
Infinite loneliness gets entangled
無邪気に笑った記憶が刺さって
Memories of laughing innocently pierce through
動けない 動けない 動けない 動けない 動けない 動けないよ
Can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move...
Unravel Ghoul!
変わってしまった 変えられなかった
Changed, couldn't be changed
2つが絡まる 2人が滅びる
Two get entangled, two perish
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない あなたを汚せないよ
Can break, can't break, can go mad, can't go mad, I can't defile you
揺れた歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は
In a shaking, distorted world, I'm gradually...
透き通って見えなくなって
Becoming transparent and invisible
見つけないで 僕のことを
Don't find me
見つめないで
Don't stare at me
誰かが仕組んだ孤独な罠に 未来がほどけてしまう前に
Before the future unravels in a lonely trap someone set up
思い出して 僕のことを
Remember me
鮮やかなまま
Just as vivid as ever
忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで
Don't forget me, don't forget me, don't forget me, don't forget me
変わってしまったことにParalyze
Paralyze by the fact that it has changed
変えられないことだらけのParadise
Paradise full of things that can't be changed
覚えていて 僕のことを
Remember me
教えて 教えて
Tell me, tell me
僕の中に 誰がいるの？
Who is inside of me?
そしたら、ここからはコラボだ〜い！
Then, from here, it's a collaboration!
いたずらに君を ずっと見ていたわけじゃない
I wasn't just watching you mischievously all the time
僕の考えを 当ててごらんよ
Try to guess my thoughts
些細なしぐさ 千も瞬き 君は手のひらに
Subtle gestures, a thousand blinks, you are in the palm of my hand
気のないふりしたって 罠にかかるわけないわ
If you were indifferent, there's no way you'd fall into a trap
甘い言葉にも 惑わされない
I won't be misled by sweet words
心の奥の奥の奥まで 見透かしちゃうよ
I'll see through to the very depths of your heart
Looking, seeking, touching, feeling... Why you know?
Looking, seeking, touching, feeling... Why do you know?
Looking, seeking, touching, feeling... I know it.
Looking, seeking, touching, feeling... Understand?
Meaning, meaning... Oh, Are you ready?
自覚なき 意思表示を 思い通りに 君を動かして
With an unconscious expression of will, I'll move you just as I want
君は動かされていること
That you are being manipulated
単純じゃないの 駆け引きのヒントを
It's not simple, the hints of bargaining
全て見落とさないでいて
Don't miss a single one of them
加速してく
Accelerating
二人の鼓動
The heartbeats of the two
心理戦は次のステージへ
The psychological battle moves to the next stage
虚ろなその目に私はどう映るの
How do I appear in those hollow eyes?
とてもきらびやかで まるでシンデレラ
So glamorous, just like Cinderella
突き刺さる視線 ズキっと感じて
Feeling that piercing gaze with a throb
君に余裕見せつけて
Showing off my composure to you
あからさますぎて お腹がよじれるよ
It's so obvious, my stomach's twisting
既に君はもう 出来上がってる
You're already all set
頭で次の 次の次まで
In my head, up to the next and the next after that
見通さなくちゃ
I have to see through it all
Lookin' seekin' touchin' feelin'
Why you know!
I know it!
Lookin' seekin' touchin' feelin'
Understand
Are you Ready?
唯一無二のジョーカー 手にするために
To get your hands on the one and only Joker
欲望さらけ出してるほど
The more you bare your desires
離れていく世界のロジックを
The logic of the world drifts away
君は楽しめるかな
Can you enjoy it?
重要なキーワード
Important keywords
全てシークレット
Everything is a secret
意のままには できないステージへ
To a stage that cannot be at one's will
気がついてるでしょう ここに居る意味さえも
You've noticed, haven't you? Even the meaning of being here
切り札はそれぞれ 互いの手札に
The trumps are in each of our hands
頭と心で暴き出して
Reveal it with your head and heart
胸を撃ち抜け
Shoot through the chest
自覚ないでしょうね 思い通りに
You probably don't realize it, but just as planned
君は動かされていること
You're being manipulated
単純じゃないの 駆け引きのヒントを
It's not simple, the hints of bargaining
全て拾って
Pick them all up
唯一無二のジョーカー 手にすることで
By getting your hands on the one and only Joker
理解できた愛のカタチを
The form of love I was able to understand
何処の誰かに仕組まれていても
Even if it's been orchestrated by someone somewhere
最後には笑う君と
With you, who laughs at the end
加速してく
Accelerating
二人の鼓動
The heartbeats of the two
心理戦は次のステージへ
The psychological battle moves to the next stage
Tokoyami Towa
Suspect
はい！ということで！
Yes! So!
ということで！
So!
ゲストはどこだ？
Where are the guests?
あれ？あれ？あれ？
Huh? Huh? Huh?
おや、ゲストはどこだ？
Oh, where are the guests?
最初からかき回してくるな〜。
They're stirring things up from the start~.
どこだどこだ？
Where are they, where are they?
フブキみっけ！あ、ミオだ！
Found Fubuki! Oh, it's Mio!
主役おれ、ちょっと主役。主役！
The protagonist is me, wait, the protagonist. The protagonist!
ということで、コラボね、最初のコラボは、フブキ先輩とミオに来てもらいました！
So, for the collab, the first collab, I invited Fubuki-senpai and Mio!
イェーイ！
Yay!
トワみっけトワみっけ！
Found Towa! Found Towa!
えっ、ちっちゃ！
Whoa, she's tiny!
トワちっちゃい！
Towa's tiny!
ちっちゃいね〜。よしよしよしよし。
She is tiny. There, there, there.
え、あったけぇ。
Whoa, it's warm.
今日の晩御飯は...
Today's dinner is...
今日のパンツは...
Today's panties are...
ねぇちょっと！
Hey, wait a minute!
先輩に振り回されてるんですけど！
I'm being jerked around by my seniors!
いや、実はこうやってフブミオで先輩たちとコラボするっていうのは初めてに近い。
Actually, collaborating with my seniors like this as FubuMio is close to the first time.
そうかも。そうそうそう。
Maybe so. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
しかも、ミオちゃんとフブキ先輩どっちも3D。
And both Mio-chan and Fubuki-senpai are in 3D.
いや、そうだね！
Yeah, that's right!
初めてだよ！イェーイ！
It's the first time! Yay!
これを機にちょっとね、トワ様からね、言いたいことがあったんですよ。
I had something I wanted to say from Towa-sama on this occasion.
え？
Huh?
何なに？何なに？
What is it? What is it?
いいですか？
May I?
あのですね、フブちゃんって呼んでくれませんか？
Um, could you call me Fub-chan?
えー！マジ！
Eh! Really!
そう、なんか最近ね、後輩たちにね、そう、なんか先輩って呼ばれるのなんか擽ったくてさ。
Yeah, lately, being called "senpai" by my juniors feels kind of ticklish.
わためとかもフブちゃんって呼んでるからさ。
Because even Watame calls me Fub-chan.
だからトワ様にも、是非ね、そう、フブちゃんとか、フブキ！なんかね、もう呼び捨てにされたい。
So I'd love for Towa-sama to call me Fub-chan, or Fubuki! I want to be called without honorifics.
え、なに？じゃあうちは逆にフブキ先輩って呼んだ方がいい？
Wait, what? Then should I call you Fubuki-senpai instead?
それはちょっと距離感じる。
That feels like a bit of a distance.
ミオちゃんたち...
Mio-chan and the others...
え？まつりとミオちゃんたち...
Eh? Matsuri and Mio-chan and the others...
あ、そうそうそう。ミオだけ「トワ様」っていいな！
Ah, right. It's nice that only Mio calls me "Towa-sama"!
えー！ずるいずるいずるい！ずるい！
Eh! No fair, no fair, no fair! No fair!
今日からトワも...
From today, Towa will also...
フブキちゃんって呼ぶ！
Call you Fubuki-chan!
フブキちゃんか...
Fubuki-chan...
フブキちゃんがいいな、でも。
But I like Fubuki-chan.
フブキちゃんがフブキちゃん。
Fubuki-chan is Fubuki-chan.
うん。
Yeah.
イエイ！やったーやったー！
Yay! We did it, we did it!
これ完全にプレゼント！
This is totally a present!
やったー！イエイイエイ！やったー！
Hooray! Yay yay! We did it!
全力でやった！
I gave it my all!
踏み出した！
I took a step forward!
イエーイ！
Yay!
こんなんでよかったのかな？
I wonder if that was okay?
よかったのかな？
Was it okay?
じゃあ行くぞ、フブキ帰るぞ！
Alright, let's go. Fubuki, let's head back!
帰ろう！
Let's go home!
はいよ、行くぞ、えい！
Alright, here we go, hup!
あー。
Ah.
色づく思いは切ないや... されど爛漫花吹雪
Blossoming thoughts are painful... yet a brilliant shower of petals
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ぱっと咲いて散った花は　終わりに実をつけてく
Flowers that bloom and scatter quickly leave seeds at the end
その時を待てど暮らせど　音は鈴虫
Wait as I might for that time, only the sound of crickets remains
そっと触れて知って　胸の内の温かさを
Touching gently, I learn of the warmth within my heart
初めてのこの気持ちだけ　抱きしめていたい
I want to hold onto this first feeling alone
暁交わした約束は
The promise exchanged at dawn
本物だってきっと信じてる
I'm sure I believe it's real
いろはにほへとの　花に魅せられた少女達
Girls captivated by the transient flowers
あはなに　はなに　はなに　落ちる花と舞い踊れ
Ah, with the falling petals, petals, petals, dance away
迷った袖でも　想い言の葉に込めてみた
Even with hesitant sleeves, I tried putting my feelings into words
誰もみな憧れる　現世の理よ
Everyone yearns for the laws of this world
色づく思いは切ないや　されど爛漫花吹雪
Blossoming thoughts are painful, yet a brilliant shower of petals
ふっと吹き消して　夜を灯す月明かりに
Suddenly blowing out, in the moonlight that lights the night
曖昧な心が揺れて　声は響かず
A vague heart wavers, and voices do not ring out
もっと冷たくて　胸をなぞる指先さえ
Even the colder fingertips that trace my chest
いつの日か馳せた形を　写し続けてた
Kept reflecting the form I once longed for
浮世の波にたゆたう時
When swaying in the waves of the floating world
うたかたの夢ははじけてく
The fleeting dreams burst away
憂いの奥山に　荒れる想い達は純情
In the deep mountains of sorrow, the raging feelings are pure
そらりくらり心揺らめき　歌う畦道
Wavering hearts on the singing path between fields
浅き夢見し想い踏み込む　この世界は
Stepping into this world with shallow dreams and thoughts
誰もみな憧れる　現世の理よ
Everyone yearns for the laws of this world
色づく思いは切ないや　されど爛漫花吹雪
Blossoming thoughts are painful, yet a brilliant shower of petals
いふみ数えて
Counting one, two, three
ここにさおいで
Come over here
暁交わした約束は
The promise exchanged at dawn
本物だってきっと信じてる
I'm sure I believe it's real
いろはにほへとの　花に魅せられた少女達
Girls captivated by the transient flowers
あはなに　はなに　はなに　落ちる花と舞い踊れ
Ah, with the falling petals, petals, petals, dance away
迷った袖でも　想い言の葉に込めてみた
Even with hesitant sleeves, I tried putting my feelings into words
誰もみな憧れる　現世の理よ
Everyone yearns for the laws of this world
色づく思いは切ないや　されど爛漫花吹雪
Blossoming thoughts are painful, yet a brilliant shower of petals
風に舞う運命の純情　咲き誇れ
The pure feelings of fate dancing in the wind, bloom in full glory
ふー！やったー！
Fu~! We did it!
かっこいい！
So cool!
パタパタパタパタ...
Pata pata pata pata...
いや、これ扇子で踊るの楽しいね！
Man, dancing with these fans is fun!
楽しいねー！
It really is!
ちょっと大人の感じ出せたかな？
Did we show a bit of our adult side?
大人？
Adult?
誰が？
Who is?
次は誰だ？
Who's next?
アキロゼだ！
It's Akirose!
アキ先輩はいいよー！
Aki-senpai is great!
トワは？トワは？
What about Towa? And Towa?
その次がまつりで！
And after that is Matsuri!
（笑い声）
(Laughing)
ということで、今日はお隣に近づいた...
So, today we got closer to our neighbors...
そう！お隣、このトワ様なんじゃないかな？
Right! Neighbors to this Towa-sama!
お誕生日おめでとうー！
Happy Birthday!
『百花繚乱花吹雪』を、まつりちゃんと、アキ先輩と、
We sang "Hyakka Ryouran Hanafubuki" with Matsuri-chan,
アキ先輩と、トワで歌いました！
Aki-senpai, and Towa!
やったー！楽しかったー！
Yay! That was fun!
また来年もこうやって呼んでいただけたらお祝いしますので！
If you invite us again next year, we'll celebrate with you!
はい。来年はなんか大人の魅力がある人呼ぼうかな。
Yes. Maybe next year I'll invite someone with adult charm.
あ、ありがとう！ありがとう！
Ah, thank you! Thank you!
え？アキ先輩はいいけどさ...
Huh? Aki-senpai is fine, but...
大人の魅力？あれ？
Adult charm? Wait...
まつりの大人の魅力といったら...
If we're talking about Matsuri's adult charm...
お前どこ見てんだよ！おいおいおい！
Where the heck are you looking?! Hey, hey!
あ、ほら、あれじゃ。靴欲しいとか言ってたから、
Oh, look. You were saying you wanted shoes,
買ってあげようか。先輩だからね！
so maybe I'll buy them for you. Since I'm your senpai!
マジで？来年呼んでくれてもいいよ！
Really? You can invite me next year too!
いや、靴なんて買ってくれなくても、一緒にやりましょうよ！
No, even if you don't buy me shoes, let's do this together!
本当？よかったー！
Really? Yay!
お金で買収するところ見せちゃうところだった、危ない...
I was about to show everyone how I bribe people, close call...
めちゃめちゃ恥ずかしい！よく頑張った、よく頑張ったよ！
That's so embarrassing! You did well, you did well!
はい！ということで、いつもお世話になってるお二人とのコラボでした！
Alright! So, that was the collaboration with these two who always take care of me!
トワ様おめでとうー！
Congratulations, Towa-sama!
STARDUST SONG
画面越し 今日も見えている
Looking through the screen again today
いつもと変わりない笑顔
A smile that never changes
纏う それは仮面か
Is that a mask you're wearing?
本当の自分を教えて
Tell me your true self
着飾る澄まし顔じゃなく
Not that dressed-up, calm face
湧き出るほど 臆病なリアル
A reality so timid it overflows
偽りは It's a sin
Lies are a sin
真実を Open my heart
Open my heart to the truth
君にすべてを 受け止めてほしい
I want you to accept all of me
加速していく 世界で生きていく 僕ら
We live in a world that keeps accelerating
聞き飽きたよ 擦れた誰かの声
I'm tired of hearing someone's worn-out voice
いちかばちかで 決められた運命ならば
If it's a do-or-die destiny decided for us
抗うよ 見つけるよ 僕である理由
I'll resist, I'll find it, the reason why I am me
可愛いだけじゃ もういられない
I can't just be cute anymore
声を上げていくんだ Stardust song
I'm going to raise my voice, Stardust song
憧れの自分へ 目一杯
To the self I aspire to be, with all my might
足元見るだけで 精一杯
Just looking at my feet is all I can do
夢中走っているよ 僕には
I'm running in a daze, for me
君に触れることは できるのかな
I wonder if I can reach you
Breathe me, Answer
Countdown the Feeling myself
君と呼応する 心のまま
Following my heart as it resonates with you
飛び出せ！
Fly out!
加速していく 世界で生きていく 僕ら
We live in a world that keeps accelerating
未知の方へ 歩むことはやめない
I won't stop walking towards the unknown
いちかばちかの 賭けだったとしても 構わない
Even if it's a do-or-die gamble, I don't care
立ち向かうよ 戦うよ 頂点を目指す
I'll face it, I'll fight, aiming for the top
そのために
For that
それは静寂の中に
It is in the silence
声は力に変わる
Voices turn into power
Oh, polar star
もう迷うことはない
There's no more hesitation
僕だけの 道しるべ 胸に刻んで
I'll carve my own guide into my heart
加速していく 世界で生きていく 僕ら
We live in a world that keeps accelerating
聞き飽きたよ 擦れた誰かの声
I'm tired of hearing someone's worn-out voice
いちかばちかで...
Do or die...
奏でた運命ならば
If it's a fate we've played out,
抗うよ 見つけるよ
I'll resist, I'll find it,
僕である理由
The reason for being me.
いつでも僕らしくありたい
I want to be myself always,
今を輝こう この空の下
Let's shine now, under this sky.
可愛いだけじゃ もういられない
I can't just be cute anymore,
声を上げて行くんだ STARDUST SONG
I'll raise my voice, STARDUST SONG.
と、いうことで！
And so!
はい！ということで
Yes! And so,
STARDUST SONGでした！
That was STARDUST SONG!
イェーイ！
Yay!
STARDUST SONGは、すいちゃんと、
I sang STARDUST SONG with Sui-chan and
おかゆと歌いました！
Okayu!
イェーイ！
Yay!
かっこよかったね
That was cool.
なんで笑ってるの？
Why are you laughing?
距離がやばい、距離が...
The distance is crazy, the distance...
距離が...
The distance...
え？
Eh?
え？やっぱかっこよくさ、歌った後の
Eh? After singing so coolly,
ギャップみたいなのがあるじゃん今
there's a big gap now, you know?
あ、確かに。距離...
Ah, true. Distance...
距離...
Distance...
そんなことする？
Are you really doing that?
じゃあMC適当でいいって言ったっしょ
Well, you said the MC could be casual.
そうだね
That's right.
そんなことさ、ね、いや、ま、
About that, well, you see...
そんな裏話は今いいのよ！
No, we don't need those behind-the-scenes stories now!
はい
Yes.
はい！では、なんと、この二人は
Alright! Now, surprisingly, these two
歌ってみたというか、カバーソングを
have been promising to post cover songs
「上げよう上げよう」詐欺詐欺...
over and over, but it's been a total fraud...
詐欺！？
Fraud!?
確かに、ね
True, you know.
すいちゃんとも歌ってみた上げようって言ってて
I said I'd post a cover with Sui-chan
まだ上げてない
but haven't yet.
Haven't posted it yet.
でおかゆとも歌ってみた、この放送上げようって
And I said I'd post a cover with Okayu
言っててまだ上げてない
for this broadcast, but haven't yet.
じゃあ詐欺三兄弟みたいな感じじゃん
So it's like we're the Fraud Three Siblings.
詐欺兄弟
Fraud siblings.
詐欺三兄弟です
We're the Fraud Three Siblings.
上げようと思って上げてません
We keep thinking about posting, but we don't.
ということで詐欺三兄弟ですね
So, we're the Fraud Three Siblings.
え、どんな...
What kind of...
詐欺師の三人が
fraudster trio...
ちょっと！誕生日なんだけど！
Hey! It's my birthday today!
おめでとう！イェーイ！
Happy birthday! Yay!
おめおめ
Happy birthday.
いや誕生日にね、やっと詐欺を終えて
On my birthday, we finally ended the fraud
三人で歌いましたね
and sang together as three.
そうだね
That's right.
動画を上げましょう
Let's post the video.
動画上げようね
上げよう上げよう
Let's do it, let's do it.
それだ。マジで思ってたずっと
That's it. I've been thinking that for a long time.
ほんまか？ほんまか？
Really? Is that so?
ほんまか？
Really?
ほんまかとか言ってまた詐欺なんじゃないか
Saying "is that so" makes it seem like another fraud.
はい！ということで、おかゆと
Alright! So, that was Okayu and
すいちゃんでした！
Sui-chan!
イェーイ！
Yay!
それじゃあ、わためちゃん、かなたそ、おいでー！
Next, Watame-chan, Kanata-so, come here!
おいでー！
Come here!
待ってー！
Wait for me!
行くぞー！はい！
Here we go! High!
至上主義アドトラック
Shijoushugi Ad Truck
目合わせ始まる品定め
Eyes meet, the assessment begins
不足したままの意思疎通
Communication still lacking
無意味な称賛 満足気
Meaningless praise, looking satisfied
疲弊の見本市
Trade fair of exhaustion
虚ろに飾る紙面上
Hollowly decorated on the page
凸凹に振りかざした詭弁
Sophistry brandished unevenly
掲げた顔が 貼り付けられた顔が
The lifted face, the pasted face,
響き渡っていく
echoes out
完膚なきまでに潰れた
At this dinner party
この晩餐会しては
crushed beyond recovery
刻まれた足跡 摩滅した靴底 嗚呼 正解を
Carved footprints, worn-out soles, ah, for the answer
至上主義アドトラック 四六時中駆け回る
Shijoushugi ad truck running around 24/7
所詮使い捨ての消耗品だと？
Just a disposable consumable, you say?
おっと一丁前になるなよ
Hey, don't get ahead of yourself
パッと打ち上げてやれ 夜を飲み込む星の華
Fire it off suddenly, the flower of stars swallowing the night
また隅に積み重ねられていく 祈り丸め投げ放つ
Piling up in the corner again, rolling up prayers and throwing them away
最高美の補欠候補
Substitute candidate for the best beauty,
鋭利な追撃板挟み
sharp pursuit in a dilemma
息詰まる下り天井
Stifling low ceiling,
窮地の袋小路
a predicament's dead end
雨にも負けず 風にも負けず
Not losing to rain, not losing to wind,
錆びついて腐食する常識
common sense rusting and corroding
軋みを増した歯車は 規格外の正義を
Gears with increased creaking, having their out-of-spec justice
見切られていく
seen through
変わり映えしない陳腐な 烙印剥がす手は
Hands stripping off the stale, unvarying brand
弾かれた枠 擦り抜ける振る舞い 嗚呼 正解を
The rejected frame, the behavior that slips through, ah, for the answer
至上主義アドトラック 唯一無二を吊り下げる
Shijoushugi ad truck hanging the one and only
所詮使い捨ての消耗品だと？
So I'm just a disposable consumer product?
おお今に見とけよ パッと仕掛けてやるわ
Oh, just you watch, I'll set it off in an instant
夜に雪崩れる星の花
Flowers of stars cascading into the night
また一つ指で押し開けていく
I'll push open another one with my finger
祈り横滑りさせる
Letting my prayers slide across
閉塞したままの感情は鮮度が漏れる手前
My clogged emotions are on the verge of losing their freshness
掠らされた理想 退廃と現実
A grazed ideal, decadence and reality
嗚呼正解を
Ah, for the right answer
至上主義アドトラック
Supremacy Ad Truck
四六時中を駆け回る
Running around 24/7
所詮使い捨ての消耗品だと？
So I'm just a disposable consumer product?
もっと意地になってよ パッと打ち上げてよ
Be more stubborn, launch it with a bang
夜を飲み込む星の花
Flowers of stars swallowing the night
所詮役立たずの代用品だと？
So I'm just a useless substitute?
おお今に見とけよ パッと仕掛けてやるわ
Oh, just you watch, I'll set it off in an instant
夜に揺蕩う星の花
Flowers of stars swaying in the night
また空に散りばめられていく
Scattered across the sky once again
祈り求め舞い上がる
Soaring, seeking prayers
至上主義アドトラック
Supremacy Ad Truck
La la la...
はい！ということで！
Yes! So!
4曲目は「至上主義アドトラック」でした！
The fourth song was "Shijoshugi Ad Truck"!
角巻わためとかなたと一緒に歌いました！
I sang it with Tsunomaki Watame and Kanata!
とっても難しい曲！
A very difficult song!
こんな難しい曲を...
Such a difficult song...
...この二人と一緒に歌えて良かったです。
...I'm glad I could sing it with these two.
楽しく歌わせてもらって...ちょっとやばい、息が...
I had fun singing... wait, I'm out of breath...
引き継ぎ大変だからね、この曲。
The handovers are tough in this song.
そうそう、本当。楽しかったね。
Right, truly. It was fun.
そう、実はさ、かなたとトワは歌ったことあって。
So, actually, Kanata and Towa have sung together before.
そう、かなたとわためもあるんだよね。
Right, and Kanata and Watame have too.
でもトワとわため実はなくて。
But Towa and Watame actually haven't.
実は不仲なんだよなあ。
Actually, we're on bad terms, aren't we?
私は好きだよ。チューして。チューして。
I like you. Give me a kiss. Kiss me.
逃げろ、トワ！逃げろー！
Run, Towa! Run!
ということで今日はね、3人で初めて出し、
So today was the first time for the three of us,
わためとも初めてで歌わせていただきました。
and my first time singing with Watame.
良かった。でもすごくバランスとかも楽しかった。
It was good. I really enjoyed the balance too.
はい、またありがとうございました！
Yes, thank you again!
手を上げて
Put your hands up
Clap Your Hands 海の向こうまで
Clap Your Hands, all the way across the sea
Clap Your Hands 届きますように
Clap Your Hands, hope it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody Clap Your Hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody Clap Your Hands, all the way to the sky
Clap Your Hands 響きますように
Clap Your Hands, hope it resonates
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光差す僕たちの未来
The light shines on our future
5! 今日はトワ様のバースデー！
5! Today is Towa-sama's birthday!
4! 祝おうトワ様！
4! Let's celebrate, Towa-sama!
2! トワ様お誕生日おめでとう！
2! Towa-sama, Happy Birthday!
BLUE CLAPPER
始まりを数えたい
I want to count the beginnings
待っても意味ないタイミング
Timing where waiting is meaningless
あの魚みたいに Swimming Swimming
Like that fish, Swimming Swimming
引き寄せるのはいい
Drawing it in is fine
まだ見えない夢を
A dream I can't see yet
この先には何があるの？
What lies ahead?
また速い予定地
A fast-approaching destination again
追いつくまでの刺激
The thrill until I catch up
でもたまに止まって Thinking Thinking
But sometimes I stop, Thinking Thinking
変えて見せるチェンジ
I'll show you a change
踏み出すこのステップ
This step I take
掴んで見せるキラキラな毎日
I'll show you I can grab those sparkling days
叶う日まで story つなぐから
Connecting the story until the day it comes true
だって君にずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to keep watching me forever
...もっと見てほしいから
...Because I want you to see more
手を上げて
Raise your hands
Clap Your Hands
海の向こうまで
To the other side of the sea
Clap Your Hands
届きますように
I hope it reaches
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody
Clap Your Hands
空の向こうまで
To the other side of the sky
Clap Your Hands
響きますように
I hope it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
Our light-filled future
今日も止まらないプレイリスト
A playlist that won't stop today either
理性壊すブレーキング
Breaking that destroys reason
何時でもいいでしょ 24時中
Any time is fine, right? 24 hours a day
君は何をフィーリング?
What are you feeling?
解き放てスパーキング
Release it, sparking
暗闇に放つレーザービーム
A laser beam shot into the darkness
輝かせてステージ
Make the stage shine
作るから
Because I'll make it
だって君にもっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to see more
手を上げて
Raise your hands
Clap Your Hands
海の向こうまで
To the other side of the sea
Clap Your Hands
届きますように
I hope it reaches
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody
Clap Your Hands
空の向こうまで
To the other side of the sky
Clap Your Hands
響きますように
I hope it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
重なり合うウェーブ 世界を揺らせ
Overlapping waves, shake the world
さあここからラップパートー！
All right, from here is the rap part!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
さあ最初はぺこらちゃんから！
Okay, first up is Pekora-chan!
いくよー！イェイイェイイェイイェイ！
Here I go! Yay yay yay yay!
終わりがあることくらい I know でもまだまだ泳ぎ足りないの
I know there's an end, but I haven't swum enough yet
GIVE ME CRAZY!
まるで LAZY!
Just like LAZY!
次元跨ぎあうの すべて塗り替える BLUE
Crossing dimensions, BLUE repaints everything
手を上げて
Raise your hands
Clap your hands
海の向こうまで
To the other side of the sea
Clap your hands
届きますように
I hope it reaches
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody
Clap your hands
空の向こうまで
To the other side of the sky
Clap your hands
響きますように
I hope it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
Our light-filled future
はーっ！
Phew!
お疲れ様ー！
Great job everyone!
お疲れ様！
Great job!
超緊張したー！
I was so nervous!
お疲れ様ー！
Great job!
よかったー！
That was great!
あー疲れた
Ah, I'm tired
はい、ということで、コラボ曲の最後の曲はブルー・クラッパーで
Yes, so, the last song of the collab section was Blue Clapper
船長とぺこらちゃんとスバルちゃんと4人で歌わせていただきました！
We performed it as a group of four: Senchou, Pekora-chan, Subaru-chan, and me!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
トワ様、誕生日おめでとう！
Towa-sama, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、この4人はね、トワが勝手に、勝手になんですけど、
Yes, the four of us, Towa just decided on her own, it was my own decision,
勝手に？何ですか？
On your own? What is it?
デビューして勝手に圧があると思っていた「圧組」っていう…
but since my debut, I've always thought we had a certain 'pressure', so I called us the 'Pressure Group'...
おかしくないぺこか？
Isn't that weird, peko?
どこが圧があるんですか！
Where's the pressure!
そうだそうだ！
Yeah, yeah!
スバル先輩とマリンは分かるけどぺこ…
I understand Subaru-senpai and Marine, but Peko...
分からないだろ！
I don't get it either!
いやいやいや、個人的なトワのね、個人的な見解があるの！
No no no, it's just Towa's personal view, I have my own personal perspective!
あー、個人的にね
Ah, personal then
そう、でもね、一緒にコラボしたりとかして、「圧、圧で」とかっていう話でコラボしてた4人なので
Right, but the four of us have collabed before talking about 'pressure, pressure', so...
あー圧感じられてるじゃん、ぺこら
Ah, so you're feeling the pressure, Pekora
確かにそうですね
That's true
はい、ということでね、本当に、こうやって先輩たちと歌えてよかったなと思ってます。
Yes, so, I'm really glad I could sing with my senpais like this.
おー！
Oh!
エモい、エモい、助けてエモい
Touching, touching, help me it's touching
っていうか、そういえば、エモい、エモい、いつものやつやってもいいっすか？
By the way, touching, touching... can we do the usual thing?
あー！あれ、あれね！
Ah! That, that one!
じゃあ、お願いします！
Well then, please!
あつレッド！
Atsu Red!
あついエロー！
Atsu Yellow!
あつブルー！
Atsu Blue!
あつパープル！
Atsu Purple!
4人合わせて、
The four of us together,
あつレンジャー！
Atsu Rangers!
トワー！誕生日おめでとうー！
Towa! Happy Birthday!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
おかしいだろ、それ！
That's weird!
ということで、あ、これ全部スバルちゃんがいけないということで
So, uh, this is all Subaru-chan's fault...
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ERROR
作詞・作曲・編曲：niki
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: niki
Illust：かかげ
Illust: kakage
Movie：Roly / とーわ
Movie: Roly / Towa
見えるこの目の涙 命の色に滲んでいる
These eyes' tears are visible,
bleeding into the color of life.
何を求めて与えた 追いかけて潰れて
What did I seek and give?
I chased it and was crushed.
青と赤と白 混ぜるこの世の中で叫んでいる
In this world where blue, red, and white mix,
I'm screaming.
何を求めて歩いた 追いかけて疲れて
What did I seek as I walked?
I chased it and grew tired.
どのくらい異常？
Just how abnormal is this?
壊れているの？
Is it broken?
壊れているよ
It is broken.
それでも息をしたい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to.
君に見えてるの
Can you see it?
夢のように最期の言葉も詰まるよ
Like a dream,
even my final words get stuck.
ERROR
遠い日のこと淡い光が空に溢れている
Memories of distant days,
a faint light overflows in the sky.
何を選んで並べた 涙色重ねて
What did I choose and arrange?
Layering tear-colored hues.
浮かぶ傍から意識の中溶けて滲んでしまう
As soon as they float up, they melt and
bleed into my consciousness.
何を見てきて比べた 悲しくて忘れて
What did I look at and compare?
It was sad, so I forgot.
どのくらい異常？
Just how abnormal is this?
歪んでいるの？
Is it distorted?
歪んでいるよ
It is distorted.
それでも息をしたい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to.
夢を見ているの
Am I dreaming?
想う君に最期の言葉も詰まるよ
Thinking of you,
even my final words get stuck.
ERROR
与えることを失うことも 忘れることもできないの
I can't give, I can't lose,
and I can't forget.
暴れ出すこのエラー殺して笑う僕だ
This rampaging error,
I'm the one who kills it and laughs.
壊しているの？
Am I breaking it?
壊して知るの
I know by breaking it.
それでも涙 痛い 痛い
Even so, the tears... they hurt, they hurt.
君に届いたの
Did it reach you?
歌う声に最期の言葉並べても
Even if I line up my final words
in my singing voice...
重なる色滲んで
The overlapping colors bleed...
壊れているの？
Is it broken?
壊れているよ
It is broken.
それでも息をしたい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to.
君に見えてたの
Did you see it?
夢のように最期の言葉も詰まるよ
Like a dream,
even my final words get stuck.
ERROR
はい、ということで！
Okay, and with that!
待って、また「ということで」って言ってしまった。
Wait, I said "with that" again.
はい、ERRORでしたー！
Yes, that was "ERROR"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
今日はコラボパートと、
Today, during the collab part and...
ソロでERRORを歌わせていただきましたー！
...the solo part, I sang "ERROR"!
イエーイ！
Yay!
なんとERRORはね、あのー、投稿してから約1年が経ちましたので、
Believe it or not, it's been
about a year since I posted "ERROR"...
ぜひまたね、あの3DLIVEのときに歌ったので、
...so since I sang it during my 3D Live,
I really wanted to...
今日、またこうやって歌いたいなと思って、
...sing it again like this today.
歌いたいなと思って、
I wanted to sing it,
歌うことができました！ありがとうございます！
...and I was able to! Thank you!
どう、どうでした？どうでした？
How, how was it? How was it?
いやー、トワ、歌、上手くなってる？
Man, is Towa's singing getting better?
勝手に...
I selfishly...
歌が上手くなっていると思っております。
believe that my singing has improved.
いや、なんか、いや、すごい実感したな。
Well, I really felt that today.
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、ということでな、あの、時間も、もう、なんと...
Alright, so, the time is already...
もう何分？もう結構経ったよね。
how many minutes? A lot of time has passed.
もう50分も経っちゃって...
It's already been 50 minutes...
はい。
Yes.
なのでね、皆さん、ここからはトワは告知を...
So, everyone, from here, Towa has an announcement...
告知？告知？
Announcement? Announcement?
を、したいなと思います！
that I'd like to make!
皆さんお気づきの通り！
As you've all noticed!
グッズが販売されます！
Merchandise will be on sale!
画像、じゃあ、お願いします。ドン！
The image, please. Bam!
常闇トワ 誕生記念 2021
Tokoyami Towa Birthday Celebration 2021
はい！常闇トワ誕生日記念2021！
Yes! Tokoyami Towa Birthday Celebration 2021!
ということで、なんと2種類出ます！
And so, there are two types coming out!
抱き枕カバーと...
A hug pillow cover and...
ビビのスマートフォンのベルトができます！
a Bibi smartphone belt will be available!
イェーイ！
Yay!
なんか画像の詳細をね...
The details of the images...
出せますかね？
can we show them?
はい、出してもらえるそうなので。はい！
Yes, looks like we can. Here!
あ、こっち！あ、こっち！ハハハ！
Ah, over here! Ah, over here! Hahaha!
はい、抱き枕カバーなんですけれども...
Yes, regarding the hug pillow cover...
ぐちこ先生に描いていただきました！
it was illustrated by Guchico-sensei!
え、めっちゃ可愛くない？
Hey, isn't it super cute?
ねえ、見てよ！
Look at this!
トワ、本当はさ、ちょっとね、あのね、恥ずかしかった。
Actually, Towa was a little bit embarrassed.
えへ、恥ずかしかったんだけど、いや、出そう！
Ehe, I was shy, but I decided, "Let's do it!"
記念だし、出そう！と思って...
It's a celebration, let's release it!
先生に描いてもらいました！
And so, I had Sensei draw it!
めちゃめちゃ可愛くない？
Isn't it really cute?
よくない？よくない？
Isn't it good? Right?
イェーイ！こんな感じです。抱き枕カバーがこちらです。
Yay! It's like this. Here's the hug pillow cover.
はい、でもう一つは、ドン！
Alright, and for the other one... Bam!
ビビのモチーフのスマートフォンベルトになってます！
It's a Bibi-motif smartphone belt!
これはね、男の子も女の子も使える...
This can be used by both boys and girls...
めちゃめちゃおしゃれなスマートフォンの持つベルト...
it's a very stylish smartphone grip belt...
スマートフォンにつけるベルトだね、になっております。
a belt you attach to your phone.
これをね、設置するとね...
When you attach this...
あのビビの顔がしっかり出てくるっていう感じのものになっております。
Bibi's face clearly stands out. That's the design.
イェーイ！で、この二つを...
Yay! And, for those who buy these two...
一緒に購入してくれたセットを購入してくれた方には...
together as a set...
直筆のメッセージ入りポストカードが...
a postcard with a handwritten message...
数量限定で付いてきます！
will be included in limited quantities!
じゃーん。メッセージが入ってないのもあるよ。
Ta-da! There's also a version without a message.
はい、このあとね、9時から、9時からですよ、ね！
They'll be on sale from 9 PM today!
9時から販売されるので...
Since they'll be available from 9 PM...
ぜひぜひ、よろしくお願いします！
please check them out!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はあ、ということでね、もうね、こんなね...
Phew. And just like that...
1時間っていうのは、早いね。
an hour goes by so quickly.
なんかいろんなトワが見せられたのかなと思います。
I hope I was able to show you many sides of Towa.
ここ1年でね、本当にもういろんな先輩方や後輩とね...
Over this past year, interacting with seniors and juniors...
関わることが増えてきて、本当にトワは幸せ者だ、な。
I've realized how truly lucky I am.
幸せ者だなと思っております。本当にありがとうございます。
I feel so fortunate. Thank you so much.
みんな、ありがとう！サンキュー！ありがとうね！
Thanks, everyone! Thank you! Thanks a lot!
はい、では時間も時間なので、最後の1曲歌って...
Well, it's about time, so I'll sing one last song...
終わりにしたいと思います。
to wrap things up.
では、聴いてください。
Now, please listen.
愛言葉III
作詞・作曲：DECO*27 / 編曲：Rockwell
Ai Kotoba III
Lyrics & Music: DECO*27 / Arrangement: Rockwell
想いの冒険を
An adventure of feelings
忘れずに全部言えるかな
Can I say it all without forgetting?
君から聴きたいよ
I want to hear it from you
何回目かの僕に出会った
You met another version of me
僕は変わりました
I have changed
新しい君に出会うために
To meet the new you
久しぶりだねって
Saying "It's been a while"
言えたならここで踊ろうか
If I can say that, shall we dance here?
好きとかって　嫌いとかって
Likes and dislikes
何度だって愛を歌う君が
You, who sings of love over and over again
恋しくって嘘じゃない本当だよ
I miss you, it's the truth, not a lie
また出会おう
Let's meet again
僕らに起きて　１に戻って
Wake up to us, return to one
何回だって間違って来たよ
I've made mistakes so many times
消えない後悔と冷めない愛情が
Unfading regret and cooling affection
恋を呼ぶ
Calling for love
恋を再起動する
Rebooting love
ほら１を引いて また２に戻って
Look, subtract 1, return to 2
３になって 愛を繋いでいこう
Become 3 and let's connect our love
言いたい感情は
The feelings I want to say
伝えたい正解はたったひとつだけ
The answer I want to convey is only one
ありがとう
Thank you
思いの冒険は
The adventure of thoughts
これからもちゃんと続いていく
Will continue properly from now on
３と９に乗って
Riding on 3 and 9
言葉とか飛び越えちゃって
Leaping over words and such
君も変わりました
You have changed too
新しい誰かに会うために
In order to meet someone new
大人になりました
I have become an adult
それだけでいいと思えた
I thought that was enough
好きとかって
Like or whatever
嫌いとかって
Dislike or whatever
何度だって愛を歌う
Singing love again and again
君が恋しくって
I miss you so much
嘘じゃない本当だよ
It's not a lie, it's the truth
また出会おう Yeah
Let's meet again, Yeah
はい！ということで
Yes! And with that
2回目の誕生日
My second birthday
みんなとこうやって過ごせて
Being able to spend it like this with everyone
本当に本当に嬉しいです！
I'm really, really happy!
恋をして バカ
Falling in love, idiot
愛にして バカ
Making it love, idiot
バカでいよう この先も
Let's stay idiots, from now on too
ずっとこのまま
Always like this
バカ
Idiot
僕らに起き上がって １に戻って
We get up and return to 1
何回だって間違えてきたよ
We've made mistakes again and again
後悔と冷めない愛情が
Regret and undying affection
恋を再起動する
Rebooting love
ほら１を引いて また２に戻って
Look, subtract 1, return to 2
３になって 愛を繋いでいこう
Become 3 and let's connect our love
言いたい感情は
The feelings I want to say
伝えたい正解はたったひとつだけ
The answer I want to convey is only one
ありがとう
Thank you
終わんない愛を抱いてたくないの
I don't want to hold onto an endless love
もっとちゃんと声にしてよ
Say it more clearly with your voice
妄想性大失態な
Delusional, great blunder of a
愛を抱いて理想避けられない
Love I hold, I can't avoid the ideal
行き場もある愛のメロディを
The melody of love that has a place to go
ありがとう
Thank you
いつまでも君とこんな
Forever with you, like this
歌ったね 照れ愛を
We sang, didn't we? Embarrassed love
数えられるように
So that we can count them
Tokoyami Towa Birthday LIVE 2021 常闇トワ生誕祭 LIVE ゲストも！？
Tokoyami Towa Birthday LIVE 2021 Tokoyami Towa Birthday LIVE Guests too!?